<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<metadata>
    <name>Unique Items Port Pack</name>
    <directory>unique_items_port_pack</directory>
    <id>2836316830</id>
    <description>[b]This pack depends on [url=]UniqueItemsAPI[/url] in order to function, and does nothing on its own. Be sure to have both installed![/b]

Unique Items Port Pack is a package of various well-known Unique Item mods, but the code entirely built for the UniqueItemsAPI. This improves on many issues found within all of the aforementioned mods alongside the accessibility of the Mod Config Menu support.

[u]Included Mods[/u]
[list]
[*][url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2489635144]Custom Mr Dollys[/url]
[*][url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2690434875]Unique Birthright Sprites[/url]
[*][url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2515446752]Incubuddies[/url]
[*][url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2523451131]Unique Spirit Swords: Xtrike's take[/url]
[*][url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2540330199]Unique Spirit Swords: Royal's take[/url]
[*][url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2814218324]Unique Animated Spirit Swords[/url]
[/list]

[u]Changes to mods in this pack[/u]
[list]
[*]Unique Birthrights does not give a custom birthright for unsupported modded characters
[*]Custom Mr Dollys has a new sprite for Ghost Tainted Jacob
[*]Unique Birthrights has a new sprite for The Deleted's REVETON mode.
[*]Unique Animated Spirit Swords does not contain unique sprites for Spirit Sword combined with The Forgotten or Tainted Eve's Sumptorium
[*]Unique Animated Spirit Swords does not yet contain unique sprites for Spirit Sword in collectible form
[*]Unique Animated Spirit Swords does not yet contain its support for Tarnished characters
[*]Lilith's Incubuddies sprite and Samson's Animated Spirit Sword sprite had transparent leftover pixels, which have been removed
[*]Some of the Incubuddies have uniquely colored wings
[/list]

Permission to host these mods on this pack has been granted from all of their respective mod creators, and as such have also been listed as Contributors on this mod. I highly recommend unsubscribing from the mods above and subscribing to this mod (and its dependent API), from which you can disable/re-enable any mods inside the Mod Config Menu and much more.</description>
    <version>1.3</version>
    <visibility>Public</visibility>
    <tag id="Lua"/>
    <tag id="Items"/>
    <tag id="Active Items"/>
    <tag id="Player Characters"/>
    <tag id="Tweaks"/>
</metadata>
